[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOT]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [TRUCK HORN BLARES]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Mr. Chan has consented
to serve as a witness.
I will get rid of Mr. Chan.
Now is the time
for you to get rid
of Samantha Jacinto.
I just wanted to tell you
something.
I was suspended.
You tarnished the Jacinto name!
You are a disgrace!
I do everything to prove to you
that I deserve to be
your daughter too.
Sometimes I wish...
it was you who was gone instead.
Ricardo!
It's likely they abducted
Mister Babot and the others...
...to harvest their organs
to be sold to foreigners.
We promise you that we will
find Mister Babot.
I know where they were taken.
I'll take you there.
Are you sure we can trust Edwin?
We have no other option
but to trust him
if we want to find
Mister Babot and the others.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
RJ, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry because I'm the one
who brought bad luck
to our family.
Because of me...
I gave our father a wound
that I can never erase.
[SNIFFLES]
Im sorry.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm sorry you died
because of me.
[SOBBING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING, SNIFFLING]
[RICARDO] Sam, it's late,
and you're too young
to be galavanting around
at this hour.
I just really want to go
to Tricia's farewell party.
Mommy, I haven't failed
any of my subjects.
Come on. Make this my reward.
Oh, Sam, I'm sorry.
Your dad already decided.
You heard your mom.
I'm sorry you're going to miss
your friend's party.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
You're sad again because
Dad wouldn't let you go, huh?
It's because Dad's
being unfair, RJ.
I hate him.
You're Dad's responsibility.
And you're my responsibility
because we're family.
Here. This is for you.
What's this for?
Just a reminder that
every moment,
we have a responsibility
to our loved ones.
We should always think about
what's best for them,
even when we're busy
doing other things,
because they do the same for us.
[CHUCKLES] Thanks, RJ.
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
"I'll pick you up."
- [KEYPAD CLICKING]
- "I'll get ready."
[ISOBEL] Apparently,
Miss Universe is being held here
this year, and, oh...
Well, I'm hoping
they'll invite me.
[MAX GIGGLES]
Not just in the Philippines,
but in the universe, right?
- [ISOBEL GIGGLES]
- [MAX] I'm sure they will.
[RICARDO] That's what I was
telling you earlier, R.J.
You know, I'm confident
you'll be the one to follow
in my footsteps.
And, son, when you become
the future Chief of Police,
I'm sure you'll be even
better than me.
[RJ] Thank you, Dad.
- Twinkle?
- Sir?
- Dad wants some coffee.
- Ah. Yes, sir.
- [UTENSIL CLINKS]
- Oh!
Damn it!
[WOMAN WHISPERING]
Sam, are you there?
- Sam! Sam!
- Shh. Keep it down, guys.
- Sam!
- Wait!
- Come on, let's go!
- Wait.
- Come on.
- [SAM GIGGLING]
- Girl, let's go.
- There.
Sam, what took you so long?
Let's go!
[ENGINE REVVING]
[PARTY MUSIC PLAYING]
Whoo!
- Sam!
- Hi!
[BOTH SQUEALING]
Oh my God! You made it!
Finally, yes!
Oh, thank you!
Sam, you're a little late.
- Sorry!
- What took you so long?
- My dad.
- Finally, you're here.
- Okay!
- Drink up, girl!
Yes!
- Cheers!
[PARTY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[SAM GIGGLING]
Sam?
Sam, dear.
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ricardo!
Sam ran away!
That girl is so stubborn.
Find out where your sister
went to party.
- Yes, Dad.
- Dad, I'll take care of it.
I'll bring her home.
She'll be safe.
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Let's go!
[PARTY CHATTER]
Hi, Miss!
What's up?
Come on, let's dance.
Excuse me,
can you move a bit farther?
Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Sir, one more.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Why did you leave?
We're still dancing.
Oh, please.
I told you to back off.
Don't be such a snob.
Come on, let's dance.
[MAN 1] Don't play hard to get.
Let me handle this.
She's mine.
Come on. Let's go back there.
[SAM] Don't touch me. Back off!
- Come on, Miss.
- Stop it!
- Let me go!
- We'll just dance!
- [MAN 2] Come on, let's dance!
- Stop!
- Stop! Don't touch me!
- Hey!
- She already said no!
- RJ!
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm her brother, jerk!
- RJ, no!
- Beat him up!
[BLOWS LANDING]
[SAM] Somebody help!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [WOMEN SHRIEKING]
RJ!
Come on! Is that all you've got?
- RJ, that's enough!
- Come on!
- That's enough.
- Let's get out of here, Sam.
[DOOR OPENS]
You'll pay for this!
- Especially you!
- Get out of here!
- Don't ever come back!
- [CAR DOOR OPENS]
Don't ever come back!
- You're banned from this bar.
- Leave!
Sam,
why did you sneak out?
RJ,
I just wanted to have fun
with my friends.
Now you know why Dad doesn't
allow you to go on night outs.
You've become a killjoy
just like Dad.
Oh, Sam.
If I hadn't come,
what do you think
they'd have done to you?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm sorry.
Next time,
listen to what Dad says.
Obey him.
Yes, sir.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Please?
[SOFT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Come on.
[CAR APPROACHING]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MAN 3] Is that him?
- [MAN 1] That's him, bro.
- [RJ] Get in.
- [SAM] Thank you.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[GUN COCKS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BODY THUDS]
RJ!
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
RJ! RJ!
RJ! [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Somebody help!
[CRYING] RJ!
RJ!
[SCREAMS] Help!
Somebody help us! RJ!
[CRYING] RJ! RJ, wake up!
RJ!
[SCREAMS] Help!
RJ, wake up! Wake up, RJ!
RJ, wake up!
Somebody help!
I'm begging you! Somebody help!
[MUSIC TURNS MELANCHOLIC]
[SNIFFLING, SOBBING]
I'll make them pay
for what they did to you, RJ.
I'm doing my best at NCIA.
I want to solve
your case myself.
all the other cases,
so those criminals
can't hurt anybody else.
As much as I want you back,
I know I can't possibly do that.
But I'll do my best
to make your killer
pay for his crimes.
Because I'm hoping that somehow,
it would bring the love back
into our family.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [DISTANT SHOUTING]
- Where are you taking us?!
- [OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
- Bring 'em in!
- Go!
- Where are we?!
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING]
Let us go!
[OVERLAPPING SHOUTING,
INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[BLOWS LAND]
- Come on!
- Come here!
[GRIM MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SHOUTING]
- Let us go!
So, what happened?
Did you clear
the operating room?
We had a problem with
one of the extracted livers.
But the next one's
in the operating room already.
Tell them to hurry up!
We have a delivery tonight!
Bring 'em in!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[GRUNTS]
- [SLAMS BODY]
- Hurry up!
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Boss Django.
Hmm?
I think you're losing your edge.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you mean?
You didn't do Umali's order
and you backed down
from Gabo.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BLOW LANDS]
[BODY THUDS]
Boss!
Back off!
Are you messing with me?!
How 'bout I wreck your face
so your mother
doesn't recognize you?!
Boss, boss.
I was just joking.
Come on.
[BOTTLE SHATTERS]
I didn't fight Gabo
not because I was scared,
but because I was using my head!
I know Gabo.
Fighting him
is not the right move.
I need him to think
that I'm not a threat anymore.
Then, when his guard's down,
that's when I'll attack!
That's my plan,
you morons!
What brings you to the city?
What do you think?
I came here to work!
My wife said
Manila is where the money is.
But you know what?
- I made money back home.
- Mm.
I had a decent job.
But she said
it wasn't enough.
Even though
I worked day to night.
It still wasn't enough.
And what's worse is that
I still get the blame.
It was all my fault.
Can you believe it?
Do you get me?
Betchay?
Are you crying?
Of course not!
Don't be silly!
- Cheers, man!
- [BOTTLES CLINK]
- Let's finish this!
- Alright!
- Yeah!
- No drama!
- Mm!
- Let's have a good time!
- Jeez.
Hey!
At least order something!
Hey! Another bucket of beer
for this table!
- Another bucket of beer!
- Enough touching.
You need drinks!
Another bucket over here!
- That table, too.
- Another bucket!
- Over there!
- [BETCHAY SHOUTING]
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTTLES CLINK]
- How are we doing tonight?
- Hello.
Someone's showing off tonight.
- Take a look.
- [BETCHAY SINGING]
Looks like
it's a good night.
[ROSANNA]
Thanks to Betchay.
She's great at
entertaining the customers.
I didn't know
Betchay could be so useful.
[PRISCILLA] You know why
she's showing off tonight?
Rosanna told her to.
No, Betchay said
she and Rudy got into a fight.
You should've seen her
when she got here.
She was a mess.
But she got herself together
after I talked to her.
- She's having a blast.
- Whoo!
Look at her go,
Madam. [CHUCKLES]
Want to bet?
The night won't end
without her making a mess.
- You got that right.
- For sure.
[VEHICLE APPROACHES]
[ENGINE HUMMING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
What is this place?
Where are we?
Gabo.
This is the warehouse.
That's where they take
the people they abduct.
That's where they conduct
their operations.
[DABOY] This place is scary.
We're getting ourselves
in trouble, huh?
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING, CRYING]
- Get down! Move it!
- Come on!
- Move!
Look!
Those are new victims!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN GRUNTS]
[BLOWS, KICK LANDS]
[BODY THUDS]
One of them escaped!
- Go! Run!
- Hey!
- Shh! Keep it down.
- [MAN] Help!
Help!
- Get in!
- Hurry!
Shut up! Get in!
- Shh!
- [OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
- Calm down!
- We won't hurt you.
- What happened?
We were abducted.
- Someone's coming!
- Hide!
- They're coming!
- Hide! Hide!
- Get down!
- Be quiet!
Where'd he go?
- Hey!
- [THUD]
- [BLOWS LAND]
- The bad guys!
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GOON GRUNTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
[KICKS LAND]
[BLOW LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- Get him!
- [PUNCHES LANDING]
- That's right!
- Alright.
- Gabo.
What do we do?
How will we help them?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I have an idea.
[GROANS]
[CLUB MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
[IBYANG] An hour.
Let's give her an hour.
I'll find a way
to get her kicked out of here.
That's right! Cheers!
[BOTTLES CLINK]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [VOMITS]
- [GRUNTS] My goodness!
Yuck! Let go of me, Betchay!
[BOTTLES BREAKING]
Betchay, what have you done?!
Hey, Betchay!
You better pay for those!
It's not my fault!
He pushed me--
It's still your fault!
Rosanna, count all
the broken bottles
and have her pay for them.
Why should I pay?
- It's not my fault.
- Matet, get the rag.
This is unfair.
Here. Take this.
Clean up your mess!
Alright, I'm on it.
Diana, get back to work.
[ROSANNA]
My goodness, Betchay.
So cranky.
Get back to work, all of you!
[ENGINE HUMMING]
[TEKLA YELPS] What are you
planning to do with us?!
[GABO] Let me go!
- [TOLITS] Get moving!
- [GABO] Let us go!
- I said get moving!
- The cops can't catch us!
Get moving!
- [GABO] Let us go, you scums!
- [IPE] Stop struggling!
[GABO] Let us go, you bastards!
They're from Caloocan!
How old?
In their 20s!
- How many women?
- One.
- How many men?
- Two.
Okay, take them inside
for the operation.
Come on, this way!
- [BINOY] Let us go!
- [TOLITS] Come on!
- [TEKLA YELPS]
- Get moving!
[TEKLA YELPS] Ow!
[WOMAN] What are you
going to do to us?
Stop struggling!
Get moving!
Hurry up!
Come here!
[GABO] Let us go!
[TEKLA] Let me go!
Aah! Where are you taking us?!
- [TEKLA] Stop!
- [GABO] Let us go!
Come on! This way!
- Here they are.
- [GABO] You bastards!
Boss! Boss!
Why are there only three?
Sorry, boss.
It's been tough.
There are cops
all over the streets,
so we couldn't move freely.
It's been really tough lately,
Boss.
We're lucky we even managed
to pick these three up.
Where'd you get them?
Caloocan. They were dancing
at a bar.
Let me see!
[TEKLA WHIMPERS]
[BINOY] Please let us go!
[TEKLA WHIMPERING]
[TEKLA GRUNTS]
[DARK MUSIC PLAYING]
Let me go!
Shut up!
[MEN SCREAMING]
[MAN] Okay, get started.
[DARK MUSIC CONTINUES]
They're pretty young.
I bet their organs are
still healthy.
They should fetch a good price
from foreign buyers.
So what are you waiting for?
Check them out.
- Check what?
- You animals!
So this is what you do
to helpless people?
You turn them into a business!
[TEKLA]
You really have no mercy!
Don't you ever think that
every person here has a family
and you're destroying
their future?!
We don't care!
We'll do whatever it takes
to make money.
You're too lazy to find
a decent job,
so you'd rather kill people
to make a living!
There's nothing you can do
now that you're here.
We're going to
butcher you alive.
That's where you're wrong.
We'll be the ones
butchering you.
[GRUNTING]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
[SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
[SLINGSHOT TWANGING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
- [THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GRUNTING]
- [THUD]
- [SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
[GRUNTING]
[SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
- [SLINGSHOT TWANGS]
- [GRUNTING]
[KICK LANDS]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[BLOWS LAND]
- [BONES CRACK]
- [MAN GRUNTS]
[BLOWS LAND]
[CRASHES]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [CRASHES]
[SLINGSHOT TWANGING]
- [WHIMPERS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [MAN GROANS]
- [GUN CLICKS]
Where's Gabo?
Where's Gabo?!
[SLINGSHOT TWANGING]
[BODY THUDS]
[MUSIC BUILDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
Mister Babot.
[BABOT] Gabo?
- Help us, Gabo.
- [GABO EXHALES SHARPLY]
Mister Babot, you're safe now.
Let's go separately!
We'll take the back!
- Let's go!
- Come on!
- [BINOY] Come on!
- [TEKLA] Let's go!
Hurry!
Thank you, Gabo.
- [GABO BREATHES HEAVILY]
- Thank you...
Gabo!
Gabo, let's go!
The other might catch us here!
- [TEKLA] Gabo!
- Help all the victims!
- Carry them!
- Let's save them.
- Let's go!
Let's go, come on!
[TEKLA] Bring everyone!
[GRUNTS] Careful.
- Hold onto me.
- Thank you, Gabo.
- Where to?
- This way!
Hurry up! Come on!
Come on, let's go!
[BINOY] Hurry!
This way.
- Hurry! They might catch us!
- Come on!
We might get caught!
I'm really against her
working here.
Not only did she make a mess,
she also smashed
the beer bottles.
What is her problem?
She doesn't stop talking.
If you have a problem at home,
don't bring it to work.
[MATET] That's right.
And she's always talking back.
- [LOUD THUD]
- Hey.
If you have a problem with me,
say it to my face.
Fine!
I have a problem with you.
You know what, huh?
I can get you
kicked out of here.
How and why will you do that?
Paquito's the only one
who can kick me out of here.
- And why is that?
- Because he's my boss.
I'm Paquito's wife.
- [BETCHAY LAUGHS]
- So I'm your boss too!
She's saying he's her wife
when they're not even married!
[LAUGHING MANICALLY]
[BOTH LAUGHING]
[SMACKS]
- Don't fight back!
- [TISSUES SMACKS]
- That's enough!
- Stop!
Hey!
[ROSANNA] My gosh!
Stop it, you two!
[GROANS]
[IBYANG SCREAMS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's enough!
Stop it!
I said stop! That's enough!
Enough!
I said stop! Stop it!
[ROSANNA] Ibyang, enough!
- Enough! Stop!
- Come here!
Stop!
Ibyang! Go home!
Romy, take her home!
Go home!
Bleh!
- You!
- Enough!
Paquito, look!
She's not listening to you!
- Stop it!
- [BETCHAY] Take her home!
- It's Mister Babot!
- We're almost there.
- Careful, Mister Babot.
- Mister Babot is back!
- [MAN] Abet, call Anthony!
- Call Mister Babot's wife!
[BINOY] We're almost there.
We're here.
Mister Babot and the others
are here!
- Where is he?
- [CRIES] Come on, dear.
- Pa...
- Thank God he's back.
[SOBS]
He's here. Miss Celing!
- Pa!
- [SOBS] Papa!
- [CELING] Hold on.
- [KIDS] Pa!
[GABO] Mister Babot is here.
[INDISTINCT CRY]
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
- [WOMAN] My husband...
- Pa!
Gabo, thank you
for saving my husband.
If it weren't for you,
he's probably gone now.
[BABOT] Gabo.
Thank you for saving us.
If you hadn't been there,
we would've been in danger.
I will never forget
about your kindness.
I will repay you
for the rest of my life.
- [MAN 1] Thank you, Gabo.
- [WOMAN 1] Thank you.
Thank you to you
and your friends.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
We only did the right thing.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Gabo!
Thank you so much, Gabo.
- [KID CRIES] Thank you.
- [TEKLA] Hush now.
[BINOY] Focus on recovery.
Stay safe.
[WOMAN 2]
Thank you for helping us.
[BINOY] Be careful.
[WOMAN 3] Are you hurt anywhere?
- [MAN 2] No, I'm fine.
- [MAN 3] Were you hurt?
Gabo, since we were able to
save Mister Babot
and the others,
I think we deserve
to have some drinks.
Oh!
That was an intense experience.
I really thought we
were going to die.
Me, too.
Yeah, Gabo.
Why don't we drink
to our neighbor's safety?
- Yeah.
- [CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Let's go, let's go.
- Come on.
You coming, Gabo?
- Yeah.
- Alright!
- Let's go!
- Yes!
[GROANS] My body hurts.
[HAPPY MUSIC PLAYS]
This Tuesday...
We can get involved in
Ma'am Sam's investigation, too.
If we get in trouble,
just forget we're ever friends.
You really came here
to face the consequences?
The case is getting
more and more complicated
because of you, Jacinto.
We'd probably be better off
without you.
Gabo, promise me
you'll never do anything bad.
Y-yes, Pa.
I promise you.
We'll buy so much stuff!
- Give me your bag!
- Help!
- [MOTORCYCLE REVS]
- This is a stickup!
- Give me that!
- [MOTORCYCLE REVS]
- [SOBBING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
- [MOTORCYCLE REVVING]
- [YELLING]
Grandma!
Coco Martin's Sigabo!